A racing second hand, shining shooting stars!
عقرب دقائق مسرِع، شهب لامعة
Conan's logic is good medicine for hearts tired by modern society!
استنتاجات كونان دواء ممتاز للقلوب !المُثقلة بالمجتمع الحديث
Today's case is of a different color! What flowers have thorns?
لقضيّة اليوم لونٌ مختلف! أيّ زهرة تحوي أشواكاً؟
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
World Art Award Party.
حفلة جائزة الفنّ العالميّ
Did she win that big of an award?
أفازت بجائزة كبيرة كهذه؟
Look! It's Aochi Marika, the actress!
!انظر، انظر! إنّها الممثلة آوتشي ماريكا
Look! It's Takahata Koji, the soccer player!
!انظر! إنّه تاكاهاتا كوجي، لاعب كرة القدم
Geez. Knock it off, you're acting uncool...
...يا إلهي، هذا يبدو بائساً فتوقّفي
Wow! So many famous people, from celebrities to sports players!
مذهل! مذهل! الكثير من الشخصيات !الشهيرة من النجوم للرياضيّين
You idiots! Who do you think I am?!
!أيّها الغبيّان! من تظنانني؟
I said let go! I was asked to come here!
!أخبرتك أن تدعني! لقد اُستدعيت إلى هنا
Dad?!
!أبي؟
Old man?!
!العمّ؟
Don't you bums even know
ألا تعرفان وجه المتحرّي
what the unrivaled Detective Mori Kogoro looks like?!
!العظيم منقطع النظير موري كوغورو؟
I'm very sorry, but only those with invitations may enter.
المعذرة، لكن لا يستطيع الأشخاص بلا بطاقة دعوة الدخول
Ozaki Midori (33) Okano Rika's Assistant
(أوزاكي ميدوري (33 مساعدة أوكانو ريكا
Wait. I called him here.
انتظرا، أنا استدعيته هنا
Now do you see?
أفهمتما الآن؟
The peerless Mori Kogoro-sama has arrived on the scene
أتى المتحرّي العظيم منقطع النظير موري كوغورو-ساما للساحة
to investigate a murder threat!
!للتحقيق في تهديد قتل
M-Mori-san!
!موري-سان
Okano Rika (28) Avant-garde Flower Arranger
(28) أوكانو ريكا منظّمة أزهار ريادية
We received the threat letter several days ago.
تلقّينا رسالة التهديد قبل عدّة أيام
Flowers of death will bloom in the Bay Front Hotel.
ستتفتّح أزهار الموت في" "فندق بي فرونت
It's clearly a prank. You're taking this too seriously.
لا بدّ أنّه مقلب، أنتِ تبالغين
Just ignore it.
تجاهله وحسب
But, Sensei. It could be real, so there's no harm in being cautious.
لكن يا سينسي، هناك احتمال بكونه حقيقيّاً، فلا ضرّ من الحذر
It's just some people getting back at me for winning the award.
إنّها مضايقة من أناس حاقدين بسبب فوزيّ بالجائزة فقط
Paying them any attention would be a waste of time.
إعطاؤهم أيّ اهتمام سيكون إهداراً للوقت لا أكثر
Who's she?
من هي؟
Okano Rika. An avant-garde flower-arranging artist.
أوكانو ريكا، فنّانة تنظيم أزهار ريادية
You know her; she's on TV all the time.
تظهر في التلفاز كثيراً، ألا تراها؟
Avant-garde flower-arranging?
تنظيم أزهار ريادية؟
She's amazing! She makes flower buds open right up!
!إنّها مذهلة! تجعل براعم الأزهار تتفتّح فجأةً
Sorta like a magic trick!
!كأنّها حيلة سحر
You could call it that, but would you also call me an art world fraud?
يمكنك اعتبارها كذلك، لكن هل ستعتبرني محتالة فنّ عالمي أيضاً؟
What a nasty woman...
...يا لها من امرأة بغيضة
Actually, the secret is in the temperature.
يكمن السرّ في الحرارة في الواقع
Mr. Shiraki!
!سيّد شيراكي
I hear you were sent some stupid threat letter.
سمعتُ عن تلقّيك لرسالة تهديد سخيفة
Shiraki Daisuke (58) Owner of Bay Front Hotel
(شيراكي دايسكي (58 مالك فندق بي فرونت
Y-Yes.
أ-أجل
I don't expect any, of course,
،ليس أنّي أتوّقع ذلك
but I assume there'll be no changes to today's party?
لكن لن تكون هناك أيّ تغييرات في حفلة اليوم، صحيح؟
That's--
...ذلك
Don't worry.
لا تقلق رجاءً
This party is for me, so it will all go as scheduled.
هذه الحفلة لي، سيمضي كلّ شيءٍ وفق الجدول
But what if something happens?
لكن ماذا لو حصل شيءٌ ما؟
It's not just this party.
ليست هذه الحفلة فحسب
Don't forget the Shiraki Group, which has always backed you up.
لا تنسي مجموعة شيراكي التي لطالما دعمتكِ رجاءً
No, of course I won't!
بالطبع، لن أفعل
I'll see you around.
أراكِ لاحقاً إذاً
What a jerk...
...يا للوغد
He's the owner of this hotel and the company that finances her art.
إنّه مالك هذا الفندق والشركة التي تموّل أعمالها الفنّية
Bastard thinks money can buy him art!
!يعتقد أنّ المال يستطيع شراء الفنّ له
His face makes me sick!
!رؤية وجهه تشعرني برغبة في الغثيان
Wow! These flowers are--
...هذه الأزهار مذهلة
Don't get into trouble now.
لا تعبث يا فتى
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Liquid nitrogen.
نيتروجين سائل
Isn't that the stuff that can freeze stuff fast?
أليس ذاك الشيء الذي يتجمّد بلحظات؟
That's right! You're really smart!
صحيح، من المُبهر أنّك تعرف
It's the Sensei's art secret.
إنّه سرّ فنّ سينسي
Is she the one who thought up the idea?
أهي من ابتكرت الفكرة؟
She made it popular, more than anything.
من جعلتها مشهورة بالأحرى
Made it popular?
جعلتها مشهورة؟
This looks great!
!يبدو لذيذاً
Stop that, Dad! You're embarrassing us!
!توقّف يا أبي! أنت تحرجني
Umm... Are you the famous Detective Mori-sama?
المعذرة، أنت المتحرّي الشهير موري-ساما، صحيح؟
Yep!
!نعم
I'm sorry to bother you, but I have a favor to ask.
آسف على مضايقتك، لكن لديّ طلب
I came to tell him it's almost time, but he won't respond.
،أتيتُ لإخباره أن الوقت اقترب لاصطحابه لكن لم يكن هناك ردّ
I see. Say, are there any spare keys?
فهمت، أيوجد مفتاح احتياطيّ؟
Y-Yes! Right here!
!نعم، هنا
Mr. Shiraki!
!الـ-السيّد شيراكي
Whose tie is that around his neck?
لمن الربطة حول عنقه؟
It was his.
إنّها تخصّه
Definitely looks like he was strangled to death.
يبدو أنّه قُتل خنقاً بلا شكّ
But something's strange about this body.
لكن هناك أمرٌ غريب في هذه الجثّة
What do you mean?
ما قصدك؟
When did you get in here?!
!متى أتيت هنا؟
I mean, look! The knot on the tie is in front!
!انظروا، عقدة ربطة العنق نحو المقدمة
That's true...
...بالفعل
I get it! The killer strangled him from the front!
!فهمت! قتله المجرم من الأمام
You'd expect him to put up quite a fight if he was being strangled,
يُفترض أنّه سيقاوم بشدّة إذا كان يُخنق
especially from the front.
خصوصاً لو من الأمام
In other words, the killer was someone strong enough
أي أنّ المجرم كان قويّاً كفاية
that the victim's struggling posed no problem at all.
بحيث استطاع خنق الضحيّة دون أن يتأثر بمقاومته
A man... and a rather large one, at that!
!رجل، وكبير البنية فوق ذلك
But it looks like he didn't put up a fight at all.
لكن لا يبدو أنّ هذا الرجل قاوم أبداً
What?!
!ماذا؟
He'd still struggle, no matter how strong the killer was, right?
كان ليقاوم قليلاً مهما بلغت قوّة المجرم، أليس كذلك؟
Yes. Like scratching at the killer or trying to undo the necktie.
أجل، مثل خدش القاتل بينما يخنقه أو نزع ربطة العنق
Right?
صحيح؟
Yet, look at his hand.
لكن انظروا ليده
There are no marks on his nails at all.
لا بقايا على أظافره البتّة
Interesting. There aren't any marks on his nails.
فهمت، لا توجد أيّة آثار على أظافره
No, that's no guarantee.
لا، لا يمكننا الجزم
It's possible to black out instantly if strangled with enough force.
من المحتمل أنّه فقد وعيه فورياً إذا ما خُنق بقوّة شديدة
The killer must've been someone as strong as a pro wrestler!
!لا بدّ أنّ القاتل شخص بقوّة مصارع محترف
are among the party guests!
!ضمن الحضور فوراً
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
C'mon, now. Isn't that a little too simple?
مهلكم، أليس هذا بسيطاً جدّاً؟
In any case, we can't move the body until medical examiners arrive.
بأيّ حال، لا يمكننا تحريك الجثّة حتى يصل فريق الفحص الجنائي
Conan! Are you still here?!
!كونان! لا تزال هنا؟
Get out, you!
!ارحل
I'd like to speak with whomever's in charge.
أودّ التكلّم مع المسؤول
Yes, that would be me.
ما الأمر؟ أنا المسؤول
I'm Megure of Police Investigative Unit ♪1.
ميغوري من قسم التحقيق الأوّل لمركز الشرطة
I hear the owner was killed. So, what do you plan to do?
،سمعتُ أنّ المالك قُتل ما الذي تنوون فعله الآن؟
Have the party cancelled immediately, of course.
إلغاء الحفلة فوراً بالطبع
You can't!
!لا يمكن
We've invited all these high-profile guests.
دعونا كلّ هؤلاء الضيوف المرموقين
Canceling this event would tarnish my career!
!إلغاء هذا الحدث سيلطّخ سيرتي
Sensei...
...سينسي
What selfishness!
!هذه أنانيّة
Listen, you! This is a premeditated murder!
!اسمعي، هذه جريمة قتل بسابق الإصرار والترصّد
I know that, obviously!
أعي ذلك بالطبع
But the target was the owner, not me.
لكن كان هدف المجرم هو المالك، وليس أنا
That means there's no danger now.
هذا يعني أنّ الخطر زال
Maybe so, but...
...ربما، لكن
She's a really selfish woman...
...يا للمرأة شديدة الأنانيّة
Still...
مع ذلك
Bastard thinks money can buy him art!
!يعتقد أنّ المال يستطيع شراء الفنّ له
His face makes me sick!
!رؤية وجهه تشعرني بالغثيان
Don't tell me she--
...أيمكن
But she wouldn't have the strength for this.
لكن يستحيل عليها بذلك بقوّتها
Inspector!
!حضرة المفتّش
I found several guests matching your description!
!وجدتُ عدداً من الضيوف يطابقون المواصفات
Anaconda Katagiri, the pro wrestler,
المصارع المحترف آناكوندا كاتاغيري
Imamura Kotaro, the football player, and--
...ولاعب كرة القدم إيمامورا كوتارو، كما
Anaconda Katagiri-sama once got into a fight with the owner
سبق وأن تشاجر آناكوندا كاتاغيري-ساما مع المالك حول العوائد
about royalties, at a dinner show.
في برنامج عشاء
He's the one! No doubt about it!
!إنّه هو! لا شكّ في الأمر
We can only hope the incident is that straightforward...
أتمنّى أنّها قضيّة بهذه البساطة
Thank you all for coming today to Okano Rika-sensei's
...شكراً لكم لجميعاً لحضوركم حفلة التهنئة بجائزة
World Art Award congratulatory party!
!الفنّ العالميّ لأوكانو ريكا سينسي
Yeah?
حقّاً ذلك؟
Anaconda Katagiri (35) Pro Wrestler
(آناكوندا كاتاغيري (35 مصارع محترف
What?
ماذا؟
Anaconda Katagiri-san. Could we have a word with you?
آناكوندا كاتاغيري-سان، هلّا أتيت للكلام معنا قليلاً؟
Later! I want some more food!
!لاحقاً! لاحقاً! لا أزال أريد الأكل
Damn you!
!أيّها الوغد
Inspector! He has an alibi!
!حضرة المفتّش! لديه حجّة غياب
This guy... No, Anaconda-san's been with his friends the whole time.
كان هذا الرجل... أقصد كان آناكوندا-سان في قاعة الحفل مع أصدقائه طوال الوقت
Several people vouch for him!
!شهد عدّة أشخاص له
The inspector's in trouble! He says he needs your help!
!المفتّش في ورطة! طلب قدومكما للمساعدة
There's a faint smell of chloroform.
رائحة كلوروفورم خفيفة
Hold on!
...انتظر
If he were knocked out first,
،إذا تمّ تنويمه أوّلاً
even someone weak could strangle him!
يمكن لشخص ضعيف حتّى أن يخنقه
But how did they get him to breathe the chloroform?
لكن كيف جعله الفاعل يتنشّق الكلوروفورم؟
Something's not right about this flower... What could it be?
هناك شيءٌ غريب في هذه الزهرة... ما هو؟
Wait a minute! When he was in the dressing room,
...انتظر! عندما كان في غرفة تغيير الثياب
the flower on his chest...
...كانت الزهرة على صدره
...was closed!
!مغلقة
Yet, now it's open!
لكنّها متفتّحة الآن
His dying was the greatest commemoration gift ever!
!موته كان أروع جائزة احتفال قطّ
He was nothing but a stepping stone on my way to fame!
لم يعد عن كونه موطئ قدم !أصعد عليه للشهرة
A stepping stone is just a stepping stone!
يبقى موطئ القدم موطئ قدم
I was never his puppet!
لم أكن دميته التي يتلاعب بها أبداً
Sensei! What if someone hears you?!
سينسي! ماذا لو سمعكِ أحد؟
Midori-san. You just need to shut up and handle my management.
ميدوري-سان، عليكِ السكوت والتكفّل بإدارة أعمالي وحسب
Who do you have to thank that you can make a living?!
بفضل من تستطيعين الأكل بظنّك؟
I'm sorry for talking out of line.
آسفة على الكلام فيما لا يخصني
Man, she's a real witch...
...إنّها فظيعة بحقّ
Coming!
!قادمة
Oh, little boy!
أنت يا فتى
They say it's almost time for the show.
قالوا أنّ وقت العرض اقترب
Oh, thank you!
هكذا إذاً، شكراً لك
Sensei. You should be going now.
سينسي، عليكِ المغادرة الآن
Yes! Here we go!
!وجدتُه! ها هو
Chloroform, just as I thought. And this other bottle has...
...كلوروفورم كما ظننت، والقنّينة الأخرى
...a cyanide compound?!
!مركّب سيانيد؟
Is the killer still going after someone else?!
لا تزال تنوي قتل شخص آخر؟
But how?
لكن كيف؟
Ice cubes?
مكعّبات ثلجية؟
Chloroform ice!
!ثلج كلوروفورم
Now I see!
!فهمت
The frozen chloroform slowly melted in the room's temperature
أذابت الكلوروفورم المجمّد ببطء في درجة حرارة الغرفة
and the victim inhaled it!
!وجعلت الضحيّة يستنشقه
And this time, it'll be cyanide!
!وهذه المرّة، ستستعمل السيانيد
But how?
لكن كيف؟
A flower petal?
بتلة زهرة؟
She's amazing! She makes flower buds open right up!
!إنّها مذهلة! تجعل براعم الأزهار تتفتّح فجأةً
It's the Sensei's art secret.
إنّه سرّ فنّ سينسي
So the closed flower had a secret hidden inside it!
هكذا إذاً، كان للزهرة المغلقة سرّ خفيّ
The flower had been frozen, too!
!كانت الزهرة مجمّدة بدورها
The frozen chloroform was placed inside,
،وُضع الكلوروفورم المجمّد داخل بتلة
then the flower was frozen.
ثمّ جُمّدت
No one would suspect a thing this way--
لن يشتبه أحد بشيء هكذا
because all the party guests were wearing flowers on their chests.
لأنّ جميع ضيوف الحفلة كانوا يضعون بتلات أزهار على صدورهم
And then, when the flower warmed up in the room's temperature,
ثمّ، عندما دفأت الزهرة ،في درجة حرارة الغرفة
it started to re-open, and the chloroform also vaporized.
بدأت تتفتّح مجدداً، فتبخّر الكلوروفورم
The owner breathed in the chloroform and went comatose,
تنشّق المالك الكلوروفورم فأغمي عليه
upon which he was slowly strangled to death.
فتمكّن القاتل من قتله ببطء
His dying was the greatest commemoration gift ever!
!موته كان أروع جائزة احتفال قطّ
If Okano Rika is the killer, who will she go after next?!
!إذا كانت أوكانو ريكا القاتلة، فمن تستهدف تالياً؟
What's wrong?! Fight me!
!ما الخطب؟! هاتوا ما لديكم
The target's flower should be closed!
!يُفترض أنّ زهرة الهدف مغلقة
I have to find it quickly!
!عليّ إيجادها سريعاً
Cyanide evaporates at 25.7C!
!يتبخّر السيانيد عند 25.7 درجة مئوية
Once the flower opens, it's all over!
!ستكون النهاية حالما تتفتّح الزهرة
Thank you for your patience, ladies and gentlemen!
أيّها السادة، شكراً على الانتظار
Here is Okano Rika's Congratulatory One-Man Show!
ها هو العرض الفرديّ بمناسبة فوز !أوكانو ريكا بجائزة الفنّ العالميّ
Damn!
!تبّاً
The ice is beginning to melt!
!بدأ الثلج بالذوبان
At this temperature, so will the killer's ice!
!بهذه الحرارة، حتّى ثلج القاتل سيذوب
Wait a minute!
...لحظة
All the guests were given flowers at the reception desk beforehand!
تلقّى كلّ الضيوف أزهاراً عند !مكتب الاستقبال قبل الدخول
In which case, the flower would've opened long ago!
في تلك الحالة، يُفترض أنّ الزهرة تفتّحت منذ وقت طويل
Was I over-analyzing things?! Was the owner the only target?
هل كنتُ أبالغ في التفكير؟ أكان المالك الهدف الوحيد؟
No, then there'd be no reason to have cyanide ready!
لا، لن تكون هناك حاجة لتجهيز السيانيد في تلك الحالة
The killer must be planning to murder someone with it!
لا بدّ أنّ المجرم يخطّط !لقتل شخصٍ به
That's not it! Where is it?! Where could it be?!
!ليست هذه! أين؟ أين هي؟
She's amazing! She makes flower buds open right up!
!إنّها مذهلة! تجعل براعم الأزهار تتفتّح فجأةً
Yes! That's it! Don't tell me she plans to kill her?!
!هكذا إذاً! تلك هي! أيمكن أنّها تخطط لقتلها؟
No good! I'm not gonna make it!
!لا جدوى! لن أصل في الوقت
That's...
...هذا
Alright!
!حسنٌ
What?!
!ماذا؟
W-What the...
ما-ماذا؟
This kid has ruined my show!
!أفسد هذا الصبيّ عرضي
You damn kid! What were you thinking?!
!أيّها الصبيّ الشقيّ! ما الذي فعلته؟
I'm sorry! I swung it and it suddenly shot out!
!أعتذر! كنتُ ألوّح به وأطلق فجأة
What were you--
...ما الذي كنت
Hey, now!
!مهلك
What's wrong, mister?!
ما الخطب يا عمّ؟
What is it, Mori-kun?!
ما الأمر يا موري-كن؟
Have you found a clue to solving the case?!
!هل وجدت خيطاً لحلّ القضيّة؟
It was actually I who had him interrupt the show.
كنتُ أنا من طلب منه اعتراض العرض في الواقع
Why would you do that?! You'll pay for this!
!ما معنى هذا؟! ستدفع الثمن إذا كان صحيحاً
The moment the flowers opened
لحظة تفتّح الأزهار
was to be the moment your life closed.
كانت ستكون لحظة إغلاق حياتك
Come again?!
!ماذا؟
Mori-kun! Can't you explain more clearly?
موري-كن، هلّا شرحت بوضوحٍ أكثر؟
Inspector. Please seal up all the arranged flowers.
حضرة المفتّش، أغلق كلّ الأزهار المنظمة رجاءً
Double and triple seal them so that no air can leak out.
إغلاق ثنائيّ وثلاثيّ بحيث لا يتسرّب أيّ هواء
Hidden inside the flowers is the secret to the owner's murder...
...سرّ قتل المجرم مخفيّ داخل هذه الأزهار
...and a failed murder plot!
!كما خطّة قتل فاشلة
Quickly!
!أسرع
R-Right!
!حـ-حسناً
We've bagged them all up, Mori-kun! Now talk to us!
وضعناها في أكياس جميعاً يا موري-كن، فلتتكلّم الآن
The method behind Shiraki-san's murder and the other murder plot
طريقة قتل المالك شيراكي-سان وخطّة القتل الأخرى
was the very theme of Rika-san's avant-garde flower-arranging...
...كانت موضوع تنظيم الأزهار لريكا-سان عينه
Yes... making closed flowers open!
!أجل، تفتّح الأزهار المغلقة
Then Okano Rika-san is the killer?!
!أوكانو ريكا-سان هي القاتلة إذاً؟
Was it you?!
!أنت؟
N-No!
!كـ-كلا
What nonsense is this?! Why would I have to kill the owner?!
!أيّ هراء هذا؟! لمَ قد أقتل المالك؟
That's right. It wasn't you.
صحيح، لم تكن أنت
Because you were the next to die after the owner!
لأنّكِ كنتِ الضحيّة الثانية المستهدفة بعد المالك
What?! I was?!
!لا يُعقل! أنا؟
Then just who is the killer?!
من المجرم إذاً؟
The person who put the flower on the owner
إنّه من وضع الزهرة على صدر المالك
and prepared the flowers on the stage.
وحضّر الأزهار على المسرح
Rika-san. You know who that was.
ريكا-سان، تعرفين من هي
Yes. It was your manager... Ozaki Midori-san!
!أجل، كانت مديرتك أوزاكي ميدوري-سان
Midori tried to kill me?
حاولت ميدوري قتلي؟
After all, only Midori-san could've rigged the flowers on the stage.
فميدوري-سان كانت الوحيدة القادرة على التلاعب بالأزهار على المسرح
But if she's the killer,
،لكن إذا كانت القاتلة
she would've died from the flowers she set, too!
!كانت لتموت من الأزهار التي فخّختها أيضاً
Yes. She intended to enact revenge and die with Rika-san...
صحيح، نوت الانتقام والموت مع ريكا-سان
Revenge?
الانتقام؟
Yes.
أجل
Her motive was most likely...
...كان دافعها غالباً
Most likely, her motive was...
...دافعها غالباً
She made it popular, more than anything.
من جعلتها مشهورة بالأحرى
Judging from what she said,
،بناءً على ما قالته
Rika-san probably didn't come up with the flower-opening idea.
فلم تكن ريكا-سان مبتكرة فكرة تفتّح الأزهار
That's right. I had to make Shiraki and Rika pay.
صحيح، لم أستطع مسامحة المالك شيراكي وريكا
My sister Haruka started this avant-garde flower-arranging,
بدأت أختي هاروكا في تنظيم الأزهار الرياديّ هذا
and Okano Rika was her student!
!وكانت أوكانو ريكا تلميذتها
But she got Shiraki to sponsor her
لكنّها وجدت شيراكي وجعلته راعياً لها
in an attempt to become the top avant-garde flower arranger!
لتحاول أن تصبح منظّمة !الأزهار الريادية الأولى
In the art world, it's natural for the skilled to kick down the unskilled.
في عالم الفنّ، من الطبيعي أن يُسقط الموهوب غير الموهوب
But Okano Rika knew she could never be the best
لكن عرفت أوكانو ريكا أنّها لن تصبح الأفضل
as long as my sister was around.
أبداً بوجود أختي
So she used dirty tactics and Shiraki's support to pressure her
لذا استعملت حيلاً دنيئة ودعم شيراكي
into being unable to take credit for what Rika stole!
للضغط عليها فتصبح عاجزة !عن المطالبة بتقدير ما سرقته ريكا
On top of that, it was my sister who came up with
فوق ذلك، كانت أختي من ابتكرت
the idea of opening closed flowers!
!فكرة تفتّح الأزهار المغلقة
And Rika decided to--
...وريكا
What happened to your sister after that?
ماذا فعلت أختك بعدها؟
She lost all hope in everything and took her own life...
أصابها الإحباط وأقدمت على الانتحار
Rika doesn't love flowers in the slightest.
ريكا لا تحبّ الأزهار البتّة
She only used them to gain fame and money.
استعملتها للحصول على الشهرة والمال لا أكثر
I learned that all too well
أدركتُ ذلك بوضوح
after I changed my name and became her manager!
بعدما غيّرتُ اسمي وأصبحت مديرة أعمالها
That's why she had to pay!
!لذا كان عليها دفع الثمن
Through this incident, Okano Rika's plagiarism was made public,
بهذه الحادثة، ظهرت سرقة أوكانو ريكا الفكرية للعلن
meaning she'll probably never step onto a center stage ever again.
فلن تظهر على مسرح من جديد غالباً
As for me...
...بينما أنا
You damn kid!
!أيّها الصبيّ
...I wound up being punished by the old guy, who slept through it all.
تلقّيت عقوبةً من العمّ الذي لم يعرف شيئاً مما حصل لنومه
Oww!
!مؤلم
There's still a good chance the criminal group is nearby.
هناك احتمال أنّ مجموعة المجرمين لا تزال في القرب
So he's the one responsible?
هو الفاعل إذاً؟
Don't do it.
لا تفعلها
You've been asked to kill that Akabane guy, right?
طُلِب منك قتل أكاباني ذاك، صحيح؟
Wow! So cool!
!مذهل! رائع
The officer, too?!
الضابط أيضاً؟
On the next Conan: "The Robber Hospitalization Case."
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Cream puffs.
كعك بالقشدة
Next episode the old man ends up in the hospital.
العمّ كوغورو منوّم في المشفى !في الحلقة القادمة
"Let's go, Megure-kun!" said Detective Takagi.
!هيّا بنا يا ميغوري-كن! وداعاً يا ضابط تاكاغي
What?
!ماذا؟